{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "860a",
      "candidate": {
        "name": "Hemanth Siva Narayan C",
        "email": "hemanthsivanarayanc@gmail.com",
        "phone": "08883963966"
      },
      "questions": []
    },
    {
      "id": "8c35",
      "candidate": {
        "name": "Hemanth Siva Narayan C",
        "email": "hemanthsivanarayanc@gmail.com",
        "phone": "08883963966"
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "what is java",
          "options": [
            "pl",
            "sql",
            "html",
            "css",
            "none"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "pl"
        },
        {
          "question": "what is react",
          "options": [
            "js",
            "ts",
            "both",
            "none ",
            "programming lang"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "both"
        },
        {
          "question": "",
          "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          "correctAnswer": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "8b8a",
      "candidate": {
        "name": "Hemanth Siva Narayan C",
        "email": "hemanthsivanarayanc@gmail.com",
        "phone": "08883963966"
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "what is java",
          "options": [
            "123",
            "456",
            "789",
            "opq",
            "qwe"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "123"
        },
        {
          "question": "what is react",
          "options": [
            "qaz",
            "wer",
            "oqk",
            "ebw",
            "qne"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "qne"
        },
        {
          "question": "",
          "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          "correctAnswer": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "dff3",
      "candidate": {
        "name": "Hemanth Siva Narayan C",
        "email": "hemanthsivanarayanc@gmail.com",
        "phone": "08883963966"
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "uihui",
          "options": [
            "uguig",
            "uuig",
            "uigu",
            "1234",
            "7689"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "1234"
        },
        {
          "question": "jij9",
          "options": [
            "gugui",
            "ubiub",
            "oiubiob",
            "oibibio",
            "5678"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "5678"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "29d8",
      "candidate": {
        "name": "Hemanth Siva Narayan C",
        "email": "hemanthsivanarayanc@gmail.com",
        "phone": "8883963966"
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "what is java",
          "options": [
            "pl",
            "sql",
            "apl",
            "both",
            "none"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "pl"
        },
        {
          "question": "what is react",
          "options": [
            "sl",
            "ql",
            "rl",
            "none",
            "all"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "sl"
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "candidates": [],
  "answers": [
    {
      "id": "4c9f",
      "answers": []
    },
    {
      "id": "c345",
      "answers": [
        "pl",
        "both"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "0418",
      "answers": [
        "123",
        "qne"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "be88",
      "answers": [
        null,
        null,
        ""
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "b481",
      "answers": [
        "1234",
        "5678"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "c092",
      "answers": [
        "pl",
        "sl"
      ]
    }
  ]
}